beebom.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | Beebom

Beebom’s privacy policy and disclaimer was last updated and posted on March 11, 2019. It governs the privacy and governing terms of our website, located at [beebom.com](https://beebom.com/). 

**What Information do we store?**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Beebom.com. We, hereby state that we won’t sell, share or provide your email ID to any 3rd party services. All the information will be solely kept with Beebom and will only be used for sending weekly newsletters or promoting services. 

We examine visitor’s behaviour on the site; and use this data to further enhance site’s UI for a more user friendly experience. 

**Contests**

We run contests on Beebom in partnership with sponsors. To participate in these contests, it requires signing up with email. These emails could be shared with the advertiser solely for their purpose of contacting you directly. 

**Cookies**

A ‘Cookie’ is a ‘Non-Personal Information’ that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our website with a web browser. It is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Beebom.com to recognize you each time you visit or login to this site. Beebom does not use cookies to store visitor’s information. Third party services such as Google Adsense and Google Analytics store cookies to track visitors and for better ad management. For any concern with a third party, please contact them directly. 

**External Links**

Beebom does provide links to other websites that are not under our direct control. Once you have left Beebom and landed on another site, then it’s their privacy policy that comes into action. We won’t be able to control a user’s privacy on another site. We cannot also be held liable/accountable for any loss/damage occurring as a result of activity on another website. 

**Affiliates**

Beebom uses Amazon associates program for promoting products from Amazon through affiliate links. Whenever a user buys a product from those links, we earn commission. However, we only recommend relevant products that have high ratings and positive reviews. 

Starting September 2015, Beebom has started using VigLink’s affiliate program which converts external links to affiliate links. Whenever a user makes purchase using such link, we earn a small compensation. However, very much like the case of Amazon associates, we only recommend relevant and useful products for readers. If you would like to opt out from VigLink, click [here](https://www.viglink.com/opt-out/). 

Starting January 2018, Beebom has started using Flipkart’s affiliate program as well. 

**Privacy Policy Updates**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our privacy policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies. 

**Questions About  Privacy Policy and Disclaimer**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this policy, please [contact us](https://beebom.com/contact-us).
